There are no bad dogs, just bad owners.
Good Boy is a comedy, horror, thriller film directed by Tyler MacIntyre.
When Maggie gets an emotional support dog to help quell some of her anxiety,
she finds him to be even more effective than she imagined...
because unbeknownst to her, he kills anyone who adds stress to her life.
Maggie, played by Judy Greer.
Annie, played by Ellen Wong.
Nate, played by McKinley Freeman.
Don, played by Steve Guttenberg.
Dr. Linda Johnson, played by Elise Neal.
Bea, played by María Conchita Alonso.
Honey Boy is a 2019 American drama film directed by Alma Har'el and written by Shia
LaBeouf, loosely based on his childhood and his relationship with his father.
The film stars LaBeouf, Lucas Hedges, Noah Jupe and FKA Twigs.
LaBeouf originally wrote the script as a form of therapy while in rehab.
The project was announced in March 2018, and the cast
was filled out over the next two months.
Filming took place in Los Angeles over the course of about three weeks.
Honey Boy had its world premiere at the Sundance Film Festival on January 25,
2019, and was released on November 8, 2019, by Amazon Studios.
The film received largely positive reviews from critics, who praised Har'el's
direction as well as the performances of LaBeouf, Hedges and Jupe.
The film explores themes of holiday, pet, animal attack, dog, animal horror.
The tone is dark and lighthearted and emotional.